It was a big scene, and I thought, "I've fallen off the wagon.
No, you didn't.
It was an open audition.
It was open?
There was an audience.
They'd call out to me when I was with you.
I can't really show it because I'm a wreck.
But now, in 8 years, I've never shown almost all of it, so to put it another way.
I think that idols were always in the spotlight.
It's totally different from the past.
Idols are...
Idols are
Idols and kettles
Here we are! This is Star Rep's kettle man, who grew up in the middle class.
I would like to call today's guest.
This is an idol.
She is Riko Ueda of X Shoujo-tai. Please give her my best regards.
Please give my best regards.
Please give her a hand.
Excuse me, Ms. Ueda.
I've come from Kyushu today.
I came to see Mr. Yakan.
Thank you very much.
May 19 is the 5th day of the tour, and you just celebrated the final day of the tour, is that right?
Yes, we just had the final leg of the tour on May 13.
The tour took place in Fukuoka, Taiwan, Osaka, Hokkaido, and Tokyo?
Yes.
That's amazing.
We didn't expect to go to Taiwan, but we were able to do a one-man show there.
How was it? How was the one-man show in Taiwan?
In January, we were allowed to participate in a festival called Taipei International Tongpan Festival,
At that festival, we had a special event, and people in Taiwan learned Japanese,
At the benefit event, Taiwanese people learned Japanese and told us that they would go to Taiwan in April,
I was so happy.
I was so happy and I was really looking forward to it,
I was very happy and looking forward to the concert, but I was also anxious about whether I would be able to communicate with them in their language,
But I did my best to introduce myself in Taiwanese,
I did my best to introduce myself in Taiwanese,
Other than that, the Taiwanese audience seemed to be able to understand our Japanese, thankfully,
Was this your first one-man show overseas?
It was my first time.
First time?
Even Japanese audiences?
Yes, it was. Some of them came from Japan as well,
And there were also local people from Taiwan,
It was a strange space, and it seems that many Taiwanese people are shy,
Oh, really?
They don't dance much,
They don't dance much, but when I told them that I was the last guest, they would say, "Oh, really?
I thought that was really interesting.
It was a good experience.
And in Tokyo.
In Tokyo.
Tokyo was finally able to lift the call ban,
It's been a long time since I've been able to do a live concert in Tokyo, listening to everyone's voices.
It's been a while.
It had been so long,
It's been a long time for us, too,
For example, we would say "ehhhh" at the end of the last block, of course,
But also, after each song, you would say "woohoo" to us,
It was like, "Oh, that's right, that's right, that's right,
I still can't get a sense of it.
It is an important part of a live performance.
Yes, it is.
I see.
So you are in charge of MC at Bakusho-chan, right?
That's right, I am in charge of MCing.
How did you like MCing?
Basically, I'm in charge of MCing,
But some of them are new members, Liloa-chan and Miyu-chan,
I would leave the stage to the two of them,
We went to prepare for the show,
I see. I see.
There is also a direction.
So, I would like to talk about the new member, Lil Mille,
I feel that the new member, Lil Mille, is getting better and more interesting.
I think she will be overtaken soon,
I want to do my best.
How many are you different from the youngest?
I am seven different from the youngest.
I see.
I'm seven years older than Miyu,
Miyu is quite mature,
I don't feel that much of an age difference when I talk to her,
Even though we are seven years apart?
She even uses honorifics,
She is not like that, she's more like Yoriko.
He would say things like, "No, it's not like that, it's more like you.
I see. That's interesting.
It's a lot of fun.
It's fun.
What are you talking about? It's not like that, is it?
Surprisingly, there weren't too many members who were willing to go in on me,
Is that so?
That's right. I was the one who went in and went in and went in,
Until now, you didn't.
You're the one who says when to butt in.
You seem to care a lot. The youngest one.It looks important. The youngest.
Oh, yeah. Quite a bit older. I see.
Thanks for coming today, everyone!
First floor!
Second floor!
Mr. Night!
Up there! Up there!
Thank you!
I'll go next time!
Yoru and Idol!
I'll practice hard for two years.
I'm serious. You're going to show me that kind of chutzpah?
This program was sponsored by Yudashi-san, Mei-chan, Ninyan-san, Umauma-san, and Bruce-san.
Thank you very much.